你根本不给我们的家庭一点支持
You don't support this family!
- 你认为支持你  - 你脑子里只能想到自己
- You think supporting the family  - All you care about is yourself!
- 就是支持这个家庭  - 我们两个孩子
- Is about supporting you emotionally...  - you've got two children...
- 但谁能受得了你  - 被你的神经病老爹
- but you're unsupportable.  - being dragged across the cosmos
你根本是个无底洞
because it's never enough,
- Jerry  - 拖到满宇宙去溜
- Jerry!  - ...by your dangerously ill father!
还要我忍气吞声
And you force me to watch it
就因为你太害怕失去他
happen because you'd rather lose them and lose me...
因为你根本不懂
And you don't even know what it's
- 害怕失去是什么感觉  - 宁愿失去我和孩子们
- like to be afraid of losing anything  - ...than lose him!
因为你只懂依赖
Because you cling and you cling.
为什么 因为幼稚的是你 Beth
And why? Because you're the child, Beth!
不是我 是你
You, not me! You!
我的天啊
Oh, my god. Aah!
初次见面 你们好
Um, first of all, hello.